<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Catch-ur-Mood</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_day">Activities</string>
    <string name="title_activity_calendar_view">Calendar View</string>
    <string name="title_activity_record_mood">Record Mood</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="title_activity_record">Record Activity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_entries">Entries</string>
    <string name="title_activity_statistics">Statistics</string>
    <string name="title_activity_export_data">Export Data</string>
    <string name="title_activity_about">About</string>


    <string name="error_field_required">This field is required</string>
    <string name="greeting"> Hello %1$s, how are you ?</string>
    <string name="title_activity_edit_entry">Edit Entry</string>

    <string name="dev"> This is developed and maintained by the Centre for Community technologies (http://cct.mandela.ac.za/) at the Nelson Mandela University in South Africa.</string>

    <string name="safmh">The SA Federation for Mental Health is the largest national mental
health organisation in South Africa. The strategic key focus areas of
the SAFMH National Office are:\n

The implementation of national awareness campaigns, Empowerment of mental health care users and mental health organisations nationwide, Advocating for the human rights of mental health care users and Mental health research and information management\n


The National Office engages with government and other key
stakeholders in the mental health sector – nationally and
internationally – with the aim of creating a society in which mental
health and the wellbeing of mental health care users receive the
attention they deserve.\n\n


The SAFMH Board is constituted by 17 Mental Health Societies from
across South Africa and the SA Mental Health Advocacy Movement. In
addition, the organisation has about 100 member organisations from all
nine provinces that are actively involved in the mental health sector.
The Mental Health Societies and member organisations are all independent
 bodies with their own governing structures. These organisations provide
 community-based mental health services to communities that are often
vulnerable and under-resourced. The SAFMH National Office aims to
provide support to these organisations from a strategic national
perspective and to a certain extent streamline mental health services in
 South Africa.</string>


    <string name="toast_pick_file_error">Unable to pick file. Check status of file manager.</string>


    <string name="delete_entry_warming">About to Delete Entry</string>

    <string name="delete_entry_msg">Uh uh! You are about to delete this entry, this action is permanent and cannot be undone.</string>

    <string name="delete_ok">Yes, delete</string>
    <string name="delete_no">Oups! No</string>


</resources>
